Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Last Stand
Episode 56
It looks so quiet here.
I’m not afraid.
Then let go of me.
We’re all on the same side; no need to be so formal.
That’s not snow.
Everyone, be careful.
The Absorption Device might be nearby.
Weslie.
What is it?
Did you guys hear a sound?
Sparky
Xi Huahua, help me!
Xi’er
—Elder —Big Sister
Where are you going?
Weslie
Wolffy
Wolffy, hang in there!
Wait, without the device…
it would be impossible for them to appear here.
It’s a trap!
Don’t go over there!
The sound is coming from…
right here.
It was all a fake-out.
We let our guard down.
He wanted to separate us to weaken our combat strength.
We have to be extremely cautious.
Weslie…
Look at me, I’m all filthy now.
Well, you see…
it was an emergency, so…
Then why did you drag me to such a dirty place?
It’s been so long; I wonder how Weslie and the others are doing.
Don’t worry; given their years of adventure experience,
they’ll definitely be fine.
It’s been so long; why hasn’t Wolffy changed back yet?
Don’t worry. Based on my years of experience with inventions,
he’ll certainly restore.
I’m still a bit worried, though.
That’s great!
Daddy can fight side-by-side with Brother Weslie and the others again.
But once Dad is back to normal,
will he still be able to use that gauntlet?
I’m afraid not.
Don’t worry, I have a plan.
Mommy, I’m coming too.
I didn’t expect the four of you to have some skill when working together.
But that’s as far as it—
You have too many openings.
Sister Xi’er is so cool!
Don’t let your guard down.
I’m right here.
Weslie.
Where are you looking?
Gone.
You have to be careful; he’s everywhere here.
You can’t possibly defeat me here.
We just need to find your core and destroy it.
Every move you make here
is crystal clear to me.
I really want to see
how exactly you plan to realize your grand ambitions.
It’s great that you’ve all come to your senses.
Then let’s go stop Blue right now.
To think you’d betray me for the outsiders…
You were the one who betrayed us.
Betrayed you?
If it weren’t for me,
you’d still be living in that world on the verge of vanishing.
I was the one who made your dreams come true.
Even though the process differed slightly,
we’ve achieved the outcome we originally agreed upon, haven’t we?
This isn’t the outcome we wanted at all.
Blue, stop this.
We will definitely stop you.
No one can stop me.
The original world could no longer sustain itself.
The only reason you still exist is because of me.
It is the world I created that is keeping you alive.
I’m giving you one last chance.
Seize them.
We won’t work for you anymore.
Ungrateful fools.
Green.
No…don’t…
Pink…
No, Brown…
Peach…
Just be good now and become my energy.
My dream…
is counting on you to make it come true.
Don’t disappear…I’ll lend you my body again.
Thank you…I’m so happy I met you…
You…
must stop Blue.
You have to stop Blue…please.
Pink! Peach! Green! Brown!
No need to be sad.
Now it’s your turn.
In your current state, you’re no match for me at all.
Where are you looking?
Are you okay, Weslie?
The sticker…
Without that gadget, what do you have left?
The Energization Prevention Device is weakening.
Wolffy…
Don’t worry, he’ll definitely restore to normal.
Mr. Slowy, is this machine really okay?
No problem at all.
But…did you hear a strange sound?
You must have misheard.
Mr. Slowy, take a look.
It brings back such nostalgic memories.
I, King Wolffy,
have returned.
It—it worked!
That’s great! That’s great!
King Wolffy is still just as handsome as ever.
Mr. Slowy, are you okay?
Where are Wolnie and Wilie?
They suddenly went out. They might be back any moment.
I need to head out to back up the little goats.
But you don’t have any gear right now.
Says who?
I figured Wolffy might need this gauntlet,
so I’ve upgraded its capabilities.
That looks so cool!
Tell Wolnie and Wilie to wait for me here.
That is…
There’s light coming through the crack in the door.
Maybe the Absorption Device is hidden in there.
Everyone, let’s go there.
Have your devices finally run out of energy?
Congratulations—you’re about to become part of my body.
Everyone…
Stay away!
No!
Hurry, head toward that glowing house.
You are our last hope.
I believe in you.
I know you can save the world.
Don’t even think about escaping.
To be continued